analizatar.com 2013-12-16

# Website analyzer, Web statistic

The Analizatar.com ("Analizatar.com") Privacy Policy covers Analizatar.com's treatment of personal or personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that may be collected when you are on the Analizatar.com web site and when you use Analizatar.com's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Analizatar.com does not own or control, or to individuals that are not under Analizatar.com's supervisory control. 

Analizatar.com may collect Personal Information when you use certain services on the Analizatar.com web site or when you visit cookie-enabled web pages. Analizatar.com may also log your IP address when you use the Analizatar.com web site. Analizatar.com uses this Personal Information to fulfill requests for our services or products, to contact users regarding changes to our site or our business, and to customize the content that you might see on the Analizatar.com web site. Analizatar.com may also use "cookie" files to better serve your needs by creating a customized web site which fits your needs. 

Analizatar.com will not sell or rent your Personal Information to any individual, business, or government entity. Analizatar.com will share your Personal Information with other entities should you request Analizatar.com to share such information, or if Analizatar.com is required to respond to court orders, subpoenas or other legal process. 

You have the ability to edit your User Information at any time, and may delete your account at your convenience. Under no condition will Analizatar.com share your user account information with another individual, business or government entity, unless Analizatar.com is required to respond to court orders, subpoenas or other legal process. Analizatar.com allows users to set up accounts to update information on web domains, such updates are public. 

Analizatar.com does not offer any content or services for use by children. If you are under 18, parent or guardian is required to supervise your use of Analizatar.com. 

Analizatar.com uses all economically reasonable security measures in protecting user data. All user account pages are protected with Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption. All user accounts must be accessed with usernames and passwords. You are advised not to share your username and password with any other person. 

Analizatar.com reserves the right to amend this policy at any time. Analizatar.com will contact registered users by e-mail, and shall also post a notice of changes on its web site, when and if the terms of this policy are amended.
